Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - M
        - MC Shy D - Don't sweat me, 1990; SR-17955; MC Shy D (Box 352)
          In same jacket as # SR-17956. 2 copies.
        - MC Shy D - Don't sweat me, 1990; SR-17956; MC Shy D (Box 352)
          In same jacket as # SR-17955. 2 copies.
        - MC Shy D - Shy D is back, 1986; SR-17957; MC Shy D (Box 352)
          Catalog # 2-86-FS-B-10; A-side Matrix # FS-3-86-10-A
        - MC Shy D - Shake it, 1988; SR-17958; MC Shy D (Box 352)
          Catalog # GR-119; A-side Matrix # GR-119-A
          Liberty City, Florida
        - MC Shy D - Fellas what y'all want?, 1994; SR-17959; MC Shy D (Box 352)
          Catalog # 12-PO 254; A-side Matrix # 12-PO 254-A
        - MC Shy D - Comin' correct in "88", 1988; SR-17960; MC Shy D (Box 352)
          Catalog # XR-1005; A-side Matrix # XR-1005-A
        - MC Supreme - Black in America, 1990; SR-21351; MC Supreme (Box 353)
          Catalog # PRO-A-4385; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-4385-RE1-SR1
        - MC Tee & Lord Tasheem - Talkin' loud, 1987; SR-21352; MC Tee & Lord Tasheem (Box 353)
          Catalog # PRO-7183; A-side Matrix # PRO-7183-A
        - MC Sugar Ray - If it ain't rough it ain't right; Knock'em out Sugar Ray, 1988; SR-21353; MC Sugar Ray; Stranger D (Box 353)
          In same jacket as # SR-21354. 2 copies.
          Catalog # MC 731; A-side Matrix # MC-731A
          Def City Records
          New Milford, New Jersey
        - MC Sugar Ray - If it ain't rough it ain't right; Knock'em out Sugar Ray, 1988; SR-21354; MC Sugar Ray; Stranger D (Box 353)
          In same jacket as # SR-21353. 2 copies.
        - MC Tee & Lord Tasheem - Gangster nine, 1988; SR-21355; MC Tee & Lord Tasheem (Box 353)
          Catalog # PRO-7215; A-side Matrix # PRO-7215-A
        - MC Tony Rone - Now dance; I'm Tony Rone, 1988; SR-21356; MC Tony Rone; Sha Love (Box 353)
          Catalog # WISE 1000; A-side Matrix # WISE 1000
          Wise Records
        - MC Trouble - Gotta get a grip, 1990; SR-21357; MC Trouble (Box 353)
          Catalog # L33-1041; A-side Matrix # MOT 10306 FDS-2
        - MC Twist - S-M-O-K-I-N-G C-O-K-E, 1990; SR-21358; MC Twist (Box 353)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # LBR 107 A1
          Lethal Beat Records
        - MC Twist - Just rock; I like it loud, 1988; SR-21359; MC Twist; Def Squad (Box 353)
          Catalog # GR-120; A-side Matrix # GR-120-A
        - MC Twist - The house jumps, 1989; SR-21360; MC Twist; Def Squad (Box 353)
          Catalog # GR-123; A-side Matrix # GR-123-A
        - MC War Flattop - Aint nothing happening here; Seven days of Armageddon; The story of glory of Castillo, let's go!; Let's talk about Brown Sugar, 1995; SR-21361; MC War Flattop (Box 353)
          Catalog # FL2367; A-side Matrix # FL-2367-A
          Flattop Records
        - MC War Flattop - Aint nothing happening here; Seven days of Armageddon; The story of glory of Castillo, let's go!; Let's talk about Brown Sugar, 1995; SR-21362; MC War Flattop (Box 353)
        - MC War Flattop - Aint nothing happening here; Seven days of Armageddon; The story of glory of Castillo, let's go!; Let's talk about Brown Sugar, 1995; SR-21363; MC War Flattop (Box 353)
        - MC Watchout & DJ Oz - Blind man's bluff; My tom tom, 1987; SR-21364; MC Watchout & DJ Oz (Box 353)
          Catalog # BR 0005; A-side Matrix # BR-0005-A
          Body Rock
        - MC Wildski - Warrior, 1989; SR-21365; MC Wildski (Box 353)
          Catalog # 612 956; A-side Matrix # 612956-A1
        - MC Xande - Rap do pobre | Funkval, 1995; SR-21366; MC Xande; Big Rap (Box 353)
          Catalog # 443.047; A-side Matrix # 443 047 A
        - M.C.B. - It's your scratch (do what you wanna do), 1986; SR-21367; M.C.B. (Box 353)
          In same jacket as # SR-21368. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SUN EP1; A-side Matrix # SUN EP1A
        - M.C.B. - It's your scratch (do what you wanna do), 1986; SR-21368; M.C.B. (Box 353)
          In same jacket as # SR-21367. 2 copies.
        - McCall, Al - Hard times, 1982; SR-21369; McCall, Al (Box 353)
          Catalog # WES DJ 22142; A-side Matrix # WES-22142-70499-VOCAL
        - McCartney, Paul - No more lonely nights, 1984; SR-21370; McCartney, Paul (Box 353)
          Catalog # AS 1990; A-side Matrix # XSM173132-1A
        - McCartney, Paul - Spies like us, 1985; SR-21371; McCartney, Paul (Box 353)
          In same jacket as # SR-21372. 2 copies.
          Catalog # V-15212; A-side Matrix # V-1-15212-X100023-B1C
        - McCartney, Paul - Spies like us, 1985; SR-21372; McCartney, Paul (Box 353)
          In same jacket as # SR-21371. 2 copies.
        - McCartney, Paul - Say say say, 1983; SR-21373; McCartney, Paul; Jackson, Michael (Box 353)
          Catalog # 44-04169; A-side Matrix # XSS171441-1A
        - McCartney, Paul - Coming up, 1980; SR-21374; McCartney, Paul (Box 353)
          Catalog # AS 775; A-side Matrix # XSS167214-1A
        - McCartney, Paul - No more lonely nights, 1984; SR-21375; McCartney, Paul (Box 353)
          Catalog # 44-05077; A-side Matrix # XSS171955-1A
        - McClain, Alton - Crazy love, 1979; SR-21376; McClain, Alton; Destiny (Box 353)
          Catalog # PRO 095; A-side Matrix # PRO-095-78-NP-3715-GD1
        - McClain, Alton - It must be love, 1979; SR-21377; McClain, Alton; Destiny (Box 353)
          Catalog # PRO 074; A-side Matrix # PRO-074-78-NP-3714-REV-S-CP1
        - McCrae, George - Don't you feel my love, 1979; SR-21378; McCrae, George (Box 353)
          Catalog # SSD-212; A-side Matrix # SSD212A-1
        - McCrae, George - Rock your baby, 1985; SR-21379; McCrae, George (Box 353)
          In same jacket as # SR-21380. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SUN 33001; A-side Matrix # SUN-33001-A
        - McCrae, George - Rock your baby, 1985; SR-21380; McCrae, George (Box 353)
          In same jacket as # SR-21379. 2 copies.
        - McCrarys - Night room, 1982; SR-21381; McCrarys (Box 353)
          Catalog # SPRO-9755; A-side Matrix # SPRO-9755 97832A G1
        - McCray, Michael - Bring your love back, 1982; SR-21382; McCray, Michael (Box 353)
          In same jacket as # SR-21383. 2 copies.
          Catalog # TOP-001; A-side Matrix # TOP-001-A-RE
          Top Flight Records
        - McCray, Michael - Bring your love back, 1982; SR-21383; McCray, Michael (Box 353)
          In same jacket as # SR-21382. 2 copies.
          Catalog # TOP-001; A-side Matrix # TOP-001A
        - McDonald, Michael - If that's what it takes, 1982; SR-21384; McDonald, Michael (Box 353)
          Catalog # 1-23703; A-side Matrix # 1-23703-A WW3
        - McDonald, Michael - I keep forgettin'; Losin' end, 1982; SR-21385; McDonald, Michael (Box 353)
          Catalog # K 17992; A-side Matrix # K17992T-A
        - McDonald, Michael - Sweet freedom, 1980; SR-21386; McDonald, Michael (Box 353)
          Catalog # MCA-23641; A-side Matrix # MCA-5667-B62
          MCA
        - McFadden and Whitehead - One more time, 1982; SR-21387; McFadden and Whitehead (Box 353)
          Catalog # SPRO-9850; A-side Matrix # SPRO-9850 Z1
        - McFerrin, Bobby - Good lovin'; Don't worry be happy, 1988; SR-21388; McFerrin, Bobby (Box 353)
          Catalog # SPRO-04166; A-side Matrix # SPRO-04166-P-1
          EMI Manhattan
        - McGhee, Jacci - Skeeza, 1992; SR-21389; McGhee, Jacci (Box 353)
          Catalog # MCA8P 2289; A-side Matrix # MCA 11301-BG1
        - McGilpin, Bob - Superstar, 1978; SR-21390; McGilpin, Bob (Box 353)
          Catalog # FLY-010; A-side Matrix # FLY 010-A S-5991
          Butterfly Records
        - McGrath, Bob - Bob McGrath from Sesame Street, 1970; SR-21391; McGrath, Bob (Box 353)
          In same jacket as # SR-21392. Different discs.
          Catalog # A-1001-SA; A-side Matrix # 11W A1001S-A
          Affinity Records
        - Braden, John - Pink Panther party time, 1981; SR-21392; Braden, John (Box 353)
          In same jacket as # SR-21391. Different discs.
          Catalog # KSS 5004; A-side Matrix # KSS-5004A
          Kid Stuff Records
          Hollywood, Florida
        - McGregor, Freddie - Reggae on it, 1996; SR-21393; McGregor, Freddie (Box 353)
          Catalog # CRT 268; A-side Matrix # CRT286A-1
          Charm
        - McGriff, Jimmy - Outside looking in, 1978; SR-21394; McGriff, Jimmy (Box 353)
          Catalog # LRC 9320; A-side Matrix # LRC-9320-A-AM
          Lester Radio Corporation
        - McGriff, Jimmy - New wave blues, 1985; SR-21395; McGriff, Jimmy (Box 353)
          Catalog # D-261; A-side Matrix # D 261 A2
          Milestone Records
          Berkeley, California
        - McGriff, Jimmy - The mean machine, 1976; SR-21396; McGriff, Jimmy (Box 353)
          Catalog # GM-3311; A-side Matrix # GM3311A-1
          Groove Merchant
        - McGruff - Make it hot, 1996; SR-21397; McGruff (Box 353)
          Catalog # UPT8P 1123; A-side Matrix # UPT8P-1123-RE1
          Universal Records
        - McGruff - Many know, 1998; SR-21398; McGruff (Box 353)
          Catalog # UPT8P 1339; A-side Matrix # UPT8P-1339-A-RE1
        - McGruff - This is how we do; Many know, 1998; SR-21399; McGruff (Box 353)
          In same jacket as # SR-21400. 2 copies.
          Catalog # UPT8P 1298; A-side Matrix # UPT8P-1298-A
        - McGruff - This is how we do; Many know, 1998; SR-21400; McGruff (Box 353)
          In same jacket as # SR-21399. 2 copies.
        - McGruff - Before we start, 1998; SR-21401; McGruff (Box 353)
          In same jacket as # SR-21402. 2 copies.
          Catalog # UPT8P 1281; A-side Matrix # UPT8P-1281-A
        - McGruff - Before we start, 1998; SR-21402; McGruff (Box 353)
          In same jacket as # SR-21401. 2 copies.
        - McGruff - Destined to be (disc one), 1998; SR-21403; McGruff (Box 353)
          In same jacket as # SR-21404. Double album.
          Catalog # UPT2 53126; A-side Matrix # OUPT2-53126-A
        - McGruff - Destined to be (disc two), 1998; SR-21404; McGruff (Box 353)
          In same jacket as # SR-21403. Double album.
          Catalog # UPT2 53126; A-side Matrix # OUPT2-53126-C
        - McIan, Peter - Playing near the edge, 1980; SR-21405; McIan, Peter (Box 353)
          Catalog # JC 36190; A-side Matrix # PAL-36190-1K
        - McKenzie, Tony - Ha-chica, 1983; SR-21406; McKenzie, Tony (Box 354)
          Catalog # S-12357; A-side Matrix # S-12357-1
          Sam Records
        - McKinnon, Charlotte - You keep me coming back, 1987; SR-21407; McKinnon, Charlotte (Box 354)
          Catalog # HAL 1241; A-side Matrix # HAL-1241-A
          Best Records
        - McKnight, Brian - Anytime, 1998; SR-21408; McKnight, Brian (Box 354)
          Catalog # MELP 188; A-side Matrix # MELP-188-A
          Mercury Records
        - McKnight, Brian - The only one for me (remixes), 1998; SR-21409; McKnight, Brian (Box 354)
          Catalog # 374633072-1; A-side Matrix # 374633072-1-A
        - McKnight, Brian - Love of my life, 2001; SR-21410; McKnight, Brian (Box 354)
          Catalog # MOTR 20554-1; A-side Matrix # MOTR 205541-A
        - McLaren, Malcolm - Revenge of the flowers, 1995; SR-21411; McLaren, Malcolm; Hardy, Francoise (Box 354)
          Catalog # 422-854 337-1; A-side Matrix # 422-854-337-1-A-RE1
          Gee Street
        - McLaren, Malcolm - Revenge of the flowers, 1995; SR-21412; McLaren, Malcolm; Hardy, Francoise (Box 354)
        - McLaren, Malcolm - Would ya like more scratchin', 1984; SR-21413; McLaren, Malcolm; World's Famous Supreme Team Show (Box 354)
          Catalog # CLAM 1; A-side Matrix # CLAM 1 A-5U-1-1
          Charisma
        - McLaren, Malcolm - Duck rock, 1983; SR-21414; McLaren, Malcolm (Box 354)
          In same jacket as # SR-21415. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 90068-1; A-side Matrix # ST-IL-835227-A
        - McLaren, Malcolm - Duck rock, 1983; SR-21415; McLaren, Malcolm (Box 354)
          In same jacket as # SR-21414. 2 copies.
        - McLaren, Malcolm - Waltz darling, 1989; SR-21416; McLaren, Malcolm; Bootzilla Orchestra (Box 354)
          Catalog # 4607356 1; A-side Matrix # EPC-460736-1-A2
        - McLaren, Malcolm - Buffalo gals, 1982; SR-21417; McLaren, Malcolm; World's Famous Supreme Team Show (Box 354)
          Catalog # DMD 374; A-side Matrix # STDM 43700-2
        - McLaren, Malcolm - Buffalo gals - special stereo scratch mix, 1982; SR-21418; McLaren, Malcolm; World's Famous Supreme Team Show (Box 354)
          In same jacket as # SR-21419. 2 copies.
          Catalog # MALC 12; A-side Matrix # MALC 12 A
        - McLaren, Malcolm - Buffalo gals - special stereo scratch mix, 1982; SR-21419; McLaren, Malcolm; World's Famous Supreme Team Show (Box 354)
          In same jacket as # SR-21418. 2 copies.
        - McLaren, Malcolm - Romeo and Juliet, 1991; SR-21420; McLaren, Malcolm; World's Famous Supreme Team Show (Box 354)
          Catalog # DMD 1581; A-side Matrix # STDM-60067-60068-1
        - McLaren, Malcolm - Buffalo gals (back to skool), 1998; SR-21421; McLaren, Malcolm; World's Famous Supreme Team Show (Box 354)
          Catalog # VSTDJ1628; A-side Matrix # VSTDJ 1628 A-1-1
        - McLean, Jackie - Doctor jackyll and mister funk, 1979; SR-21422; McLean, Jackie (Box 354)
          Catalog # JD-11570; A-side Matrix # PD-11570A-1
        - MCM 13 - Versatile styles the EP volume III, 1997; SR-21423; MCM 13 (Box 354)
          Catalog # NRG-113; A-side Matrix # NRG 113-A
          Jasper Stone Trax
        - McPherson, David - You can't stop!, 1982; SR-21424; McPherson, David (Box 354)
          Catalog # S-12349; A-side Matrix # S-12349-1-1
        - McRae, Gwen - Funky sensation, 1981; SR-21425; McRae, Gwen (Box 354)
          Catalog # DMD 286; A-side Matrix # STDM-40254-2
        - McWilliams, Brigette - I get the job done, 1994; SR-21426; McWilliams, Brigette (Box 354)
          Catalog # SPRO-14179; A-side Matrix # Y-38437-A
        - McWilliams, Brigette - I get the job done, 1994; SR-21427; McWilliams, Brigette (Box 354)
          Catalog # Y-38437; A-side Matrix # Y-38437-A
        - McWilliams, Brigette - Fire, 1997; SR-21428; McWilliams, Brigette (Box 354)
          Catalog # SPRO-12224; A-side Matrix # SPRO-12224-A-1
        - M-D-Emm - Get hip to this (shy boys remixes), 1989; SR-21429; M-D-Emm; Nasih (Box 354)
          Catalog # LICT 022R; A-side Matrix # LICT-022R-HH1
          Republic Records
        - M.D.S. Production - Because I'm a pro, 1988; SR-21430; M.D.S. Production (Box 354)
          Catalog # U.S.P. 152; A-side Matrix # USP 152-A
          Universal Sound Productions, Inc
        - Me & My Cousin - International (disc one), 1996; SR-21431; Me & My Cousin (Box 354)
          In same jacket as # SR-21432. Double album.
          Catalog # P1 53558; A-side Matrix # P1-53558-A
        - Me & My Cousin - International (disc two), 1996; SR-21432; Me & My Cousin (Box 354)
          In same jacket as # SR-21431. Double album.
          Catalog # P1 53558; A-side Matrix # P1-53558-C
        - Me & My Cousin - Red carpet; Learnin' the game, 1995; SR-21433; Me & My Cousin (Box 354)
          Catalog # SPRO 50916; A-side Matrix # PVL 53221-A
        - Me & My Cousin - Smooth, 1996; SR-21434; Me & My Cousin (Box 354)
          Catalog # SPRO 30032; A-side Matrix # SPRO-30032-A
        - Me & My Cousin - Red carpet; Learnin' the game, 1995; SR-21435; Me & My Cousin (Box 354)
        - Me & My Cousin - Smooth, 1996; SR-21436; Me & My Cousin (Box 354)
        - Me Phi Me - Black sunshine, 1992; SR-21437; Me Phi Me (Box 354)
          Catalog # 74321 122231; A-side Matrix # 74321 122231 A-01-01-1
        - Mea Culpa - Spiritual light; Mea Culpa, 1998; SR-21438; Mea Culpa (Box 354)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # TREE 007-A
          Four D Recordings
        - Mead, Abigail - Full metal jacket (I wanna be your drill instructor); Sniper, 1987; SR-21439; Mead, Abigail; Goulding, Nigel (Box 354)
          In same jacket as # SR-21440. 2 copies.
          Catalog # W 8187; A-side Matrix # W8187T-A3
        - Mead, Abigail - Full metal jacket (I wanna be your drill instructor); Sniper, 1987; SR-21440; Mead, Abigail; Goulding, Nigel (Box 354)
          In same jacket as # SR-21439. 2 copies.
        - Mean Machine - Disco dream, 1981; SR-21441; Mean Machine (Box 354)
          In same jacket as # SR-21442. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SH-564; A-side Matrix # VID-212-A
          Sugar Hill
          Englewood, New Jersey
        - Mean Machine - Disco dream, 1981; SR-21442; Mean Machine (Box 354)
          In same jacket as # SR-21441. 2 copies.
        - Meaner - Reap rap song, 1996; SR-21443; Meaner (Box 354)
          Catalog # PR12 7323-1; A-side Matrix # PR-12-7323-1 RE2
          Loose Cannon
        - Mean Beat Manifesto - Storm the studio (disc one), 1989; SR-21444; Mean Beat Manifesto (Box 354)
          In same jacket as # SR-21445. Double album.
          Catalog # SDX 040; A-side Matrix # LYN-22224
          Sweatbox Records
        - Mean Beat Manifesto - Storm the studio (disc two), 1989; SR-21445; Mean Beat Manifesto (Box 354)
          In same jacket as # SR-21444. Double album.
          Catalog # SDX 040; A-side Matrix # LYN-22236
        - Mean Beat Manifesto - Suck hard, 1987; SR-21446; Mean Beat Manifesto (Box 354)
          Catalog # SOX 023; A-side Matrix # SOX-023-R-A-1
        - Meat Loaf - Dead ringer, 1981; SR-21447; Meat Loaf (Box 354)
          Catalog # FE 36007; A-side Matrix # AL-36007-GA
        - Meco - Moondancer, 1979; SR-21448; Meco (Box 354)
          In same jacket as # SR-21449. 2 copies.
          Catalog # NBLP 7155; A-side Matrix # NBLP-7155-AS-PRC2
        - Meco - Moondancer, 1979; SR-21449; Meco (Box 354)
          In same jacket as # SR-21448. 2 copies.
          Catalog # NBLP 7155; A-side Matrix # NBLP-7155-AS-K1
        - Meco - Encounters of every kind, 1977; SR-21450; Meco (Box 354)
          Catalog # MNLP 8004; A-side Matrix # MNLP-8004-A-14
          Millenium
        - Meco - The Wizard of Oz (special disco version), 1978; SR-21451; Meco (Box 354)
          Catalog # MND-20621; A-side Matrix # MND-20621-R1
        - Medard, Rachel - Break free | This is carnaval, 2000; SR-21452; Medard, Rachel; Y.J. Paris (Box 354)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # BR4001-A
          Calang
          Richmond Hill, New York
        - Medeiros, Elli - A bailar calypso, 1987; SR-21453; Medeiros, Elli (Box 354)
          Catalog # 885 578-1; A-side Matrix # 222 8855781 A PDO
        - Medici, Robert - Peri pherial vision, 1982; SR-21454; Medici, Robert (Box 354)
          Catalog # LR-1116; A-side Matrix # LR116A
          Limo Records
        - Meeno - I'm that n**** | Vacant lot goes no limit, 2000; SR-21455; Meeno; Floss, Dave; Montane, Emoni (Box 354)
          Catalog # SPRO 81337; A-side Matrix # 81337-14 RE3-A
        - Meg - Lover girl, 1989; SR-21456; Meg (Box 354)
          Catalog # HAL 12151; A-side Matrix # HAL-12151-A
          Musicworks Records
        - Mekon - Revenge of the mekon, 1995; SR-21457; Mekon (Box 354)
          Catalog # WALLT 012; A-side Matrix # WALLT 012 A1
          Wall Of Sound
        - Mekon - Skool's out, 1997; SR-21458; Mekon; Schoolly D (Box 354)
          Catalog # WALLT 027; A-side Matrix # WAAL-T-027-A1
        - Mekon - D-funktional, 2003; SR-21459; Mekon; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 354)
          Catalog # WALLT 092; A-side Matrix # WALLT 092
        - Mekon - Phatty's lunchbox, 1997; SR-21460; Mekon (Box 354)
          Catalog # WALLT 032; A-side Matrix # WALL T 032-A
        - Melaaz - Non, non, non, 1994; SR-21461; Melaaz (Box 354)
          Catalog # MELAAZ 1; A-side Matrix # MELAAZ 1
          BMG
        - Melaaz - Je marche en solitaire, 1995; SR-21462; Melaaz (Box 354)
          In same jacket as # SR-21463. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 74321279501; A-side Matrix # MPO 74321279501 A1
        - Melaaz - Je marche en solitaire, 1995; SR-21463; Melaaz (Box 354)
          In same jacket as # SR-21462. 2 copies.
        - Melaaz - Le seul remede, 1996; SR-21464; Melaaz (Box 355)
          In same jacket as # SR-21465. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 74321342451; A-side Matrix # MPO 134245-1 A
        - Melaaz - Le seul remede, 1996; SR-21465; Melaaz (Box 355)
          In same jacket as # SR-21464. 2 copies.
        - Melanie - The four sides of Melanie (disc one), 1972; SR-21466; Melanie (Box 355)
          In same jacket as # SR-21467. Double album.
          Catalog # BDS-95005; A-side Matrix # BDS-95005A-4
          Buddah Records
        - Melanie - The four sides of Melanie (disc two), 1972; SR-21467; Melanie (Box 355)
          In same jacket as # SR-21466. Double album.
          Catalog # BDS-95005; A-side Matrix # BDS-95005B-4
        - Melanie - Candles in the rain, 1970; SR-21468; Melanie (Box 355)
          Catalog # BDS 5060; A-side Matrix # BDS 5060A
        - Melanie - Candles in the rain, 1970; SR-21469; Melanie (Box 355)
        - Melendez, Lisette - Time passes by, 1996; SR-21470; Melendez, Lisette (Box 355)
          Catalog # WAR-209; A-side Matrix # WAR-209-A
        - Melendez, Lisette - Will you ever save me, 1993; SR-21471; Melendez, Lisette (Box 355)
          Catalog # OAS 5980; A-side Matrix # XSS-05980-A-1A
        - Melendez, Lisette - Together forever, 1990; SR-21472; Melendez, Lisette (Box 355)
          Catalog # 44 73630; A-side Matrix # XSS-73630A
        - Melle Mel - Mama, 1997; SR-21473; Melle Mel; Grandmaster Mele-Mel; Scorpio (Box 355)
          Catalog # STG 1208-1; A-side Matrix # PAP 3-DJS-12081-A-1A
          Str8 Game Records
        - Melle Mel - Beat street; Internationally known, 1984; SR-21474; Melle Mel; Grandmaster Melle Mel; Furious Five; Mr. Ness (Box 355)
          Catalog # SH 32019; A-side Matrix # VID-227-A
        - Melle Mel - Jesse, 1984; SR-21475; Melle Mel; Grandmaster Melle Mel (Box 355)
          Catalog # SH-32016; A-side Matrix # SH-274-A
        - Melle Mel - Step off, 1985; SR-21476; Melle Mel; Grandmaster Melle Mel; Furious Five (Box 355)
          Catalog # SUGLP 9001; A-side Matrix # SUGLP 9001 A CG
        - Melle Mel - King of the streets, 1985; SR-21477; Melle Mel; Grandmaster Melle Mel (Box 355)
          Catalog # SH-32044; A-side Matrix # VID-301-A
        - Die Hard - You know; Don't stop, 2002; SR-21478; Die Hard; Melle Mel; Rondo (Box 355)
          Catalog # PT102; A-side Matrix # PT102-A
          Phat Trax
        - Mello, Humberto - Funk melody II, 1995; SR-21479; Mello, Humberto (Box 355)
          Catalog # 443.016; A-side Matrix # 443016 A
        - Mellow Yellow - Herpes takes over, 1982; SR-21480; Mellow Yellow; Young Ranks (Box 355)
          Catalog # J-387; A-side Matrix # JAMROCK-1982-A
          Jam Rock Records
        - Melody Makers - What a plot; Children playing in the street, 1982; SR-21481; Melody Makers; Marley, David (Box 355)
          Catalog # Shanachie-5006; A-side Matrix # SH-5006-A
          Shanachie
        - Melvin, Harold - I really love you, 1984; SR-21482; Melvin, Harold; Blue Notes (Box 355)
          Catalog # DMD 780; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-46748-1
          Philly World Records
        - Melvin, Harold - Wake up everybody, 1975; SR-21483; Melvin, Harold; Blue Notes (Box 355)
          Catalog # PZ 33808; A-side Matrix # PIR AL-33808-1
          Philadelphia International Records
        - Members - Radio, 1982; SR-21484; Members (Box 355)
          Catalog # CP 720; A-side Matrix # CP-720-SA
        - Members of Mayday - The bells of reformation, 1995; SR-21485; Members of Mayday (Box 355)
          Catalog # 851 977-1; A-side Matrix # 851 977-1 A
        - Members of Mars - Live from Mars, 1996; SR-21486; Members of Mars (Box 355)
          Catalog # 573 141-1; A-side Matrix # 573 141-1 A
        - Members of Mayday - 10 in 10, 2001; SR-21487; Members of Mayday (Box 355)